Hallelujah!
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
You may be seated. Thank you.
Hallelujah.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
This is another day - another day of breakthrough.
Free spirit - that is, a heart without unforgiveness, anger, bitterness,
pain of the past, bad feelings towards others.
Tell your neighbour:
Heart without unforgiveness, bitterness, anger, pain of the past, bad feelings towards others.
That is where your problem is.
Free spirit.
Spirit means heart.
Heart without unforgiveness.
Heart without bitterness.
Heart without envy.
Heart without bad feelings towards others.
Whether you are right or wrong.
Bad feelings - whether the person wronged you or not.
Heart without bad feelings towards others.
Inner my heart
Lord I want to be like Jesus inner my heart
Everything about you suggests unforgiveness.
Your political party - Republican, Democrat, APC, ADP - they are holding offence against themselves.
Your business partner - offence against others.
Country to country - offence against others.
This is why, any step you take, you are taking it into darkness.
Tell your neighbour, "Any step we take, we are taking it into darkness
because everything about us suggests unforgiveness".
That you are rich now does not mean you are rich until the end.
That you are superior now does not mean you are superior until the end.
The beginner is not the owner but the finisher.
Since you were born, can you point to me someone in your family who started it and ended it?
Started big and ended big.
Everyone is fading away.
What is the cause? Offence, unforgiveness, bitterness, bad feelings towards others.
Anyone who cannot forgive is hurting himself more than anyone.
Holding grudges, holding bitterness damages hearts.
Holding unforgiveness damages hearts.
Any step you take, you are taking it into darkness.
Tell your neighbour, "Holding unforgiveness, holding bad feelings towards others damages our spirits".
The Spirit of God expresses Himself through our spirit.
There is nowhere He can express Himself because you have damaged your heart.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
TT: Anonymous
RV: Mel Flowers 28/12/2018